Finding Aid for the William Campbell Binkley Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- 1 roll of microfilm, unidentified (Box 40 (7))
STUART, W. S. - 1 (Kay 17, 1933)
SUMMERS, Festus P. (West Virginia War History Commission) - 1 (June 30, 1945)
SUMMERSELL, Charles G. (University of Alabama) - 52 (1931-33, 1936-40, 1945, 1946, 1948, 1950, 1956-59)
SUNSHINE Club - 1 (n.d.)
SWAIN, Martha, and Susie Gordon - 1 (n.d.)
SWANTON, Emily - 1 (Aug. 23, 1957)
SWART, C --- ) - 1 (June 16, 1922)
SWEARINGS, Mack (Tulane University, Georgia State College for Women) -7 (1935, 1939, 1942)
SWEENEY, Thomas B. (Equitable Life Assurance Society) - 1 (Jan. 29, 1940)
SWEET, Alfred H. - 1 (Nov. 28, 1949)
SWEM, E. G. (College of William and Mary Library) - 2 (1943)
SWINT, Betty W. (College and Research Libraries) - 6 (1937, 1945, 1946, 1967)
SWINT, Henry Lee (Middle Georgia College, Vanderbilt University) - 142 (1936, 1941, 1942, 1944, 1946, 1949-62, 1965, 1967, 1968)
SWINT, Thyra L. - 1 (Mar. 25, 1945)
SYDNOR, Charles L. (University of Mississippi, Duke University) - 17 (1935, 1939, 1942, 1943, 1945, 1947-49)
TAGGART, Harold F. (Santa Maria Union High School, San Mateo Junior College) - 2 (1922, 1931)
TAMEY, C. W. (Gooding College) - 1 (Dec. 3, 1928)
TANDY, Lucy (University of Oklahoma) - 1 (Nov. 13, 1951)
TATUM, Georgia Lee (Mississippi Delta State Teachers College) - 10 (1931-34, 1938)
TAYLOR, A. Elizabeth (Judson College, Texas State College for Women, Texas Women's University) - 23 (1941, 1943-47, 1950, 1952, 1953, 1955, 1957, 1960, 1963)
TEBEAU, C. W. (University of Miami) - 1 (Jan. 28, 1950)
TECHNICAL Composition Co. - 1 (July 22, 1947)
TEN H00R, Marten (Tulane University, University of Alabama) - 3 (1938, 1953)
TENNESSEE Electric Power Company (J.A. Hutchison) - 1 (July 17, 1936)
TENNESSEE Valley Authority (C. L. rtichey) - 1 (Nov. 9, 1933)
THOMAS, Alfred B. (University of Oklahoma) - 4 (1936, 1938, 1939)
THOMAS, Bruce (Trinity University) - 1 (Mar. 12, 1953)
THOMAS, Charles M. (Army Air Forces) - 1 (Oct. 26, 1944)
THOMAS, David Y. (University of Arkansas, University of Texas) - 9 (1920, 1931, 1932, 1934, 1937, 1939, 1942)
THOMAS, Francis W. (Harvard Law School) - 3 (1926-28)
THOMAS, Homer L. (Camp Winnepe) - 1 (Feb. 3, 1937)
THOMAS, Lois (Arkansas History Commission) - 3 (1935, 1937)
THOMPSON, E. Bruce (Mississippi College, Baylor University) - 20 (1935, 1942-48, 1950, 1965)
THOMPSON, Lawrence S. (University of Kentucky Libraries) - 1 (Feb. 14, 1950)
THOMPSON, S. B. - 2 (1938, 1942) (including 1 from D. S. Campbell)
THOMSON, Bob Polk - 1 (Feb. 15, 1949)
THOMSON, Phillip - 1 (July 29, 1960)
THORNHILL, Bonnie (Texas State Historical Association) - 1 (Aug. 5, 1953)
THORNTON, Henrietta (Indiana University) - 2 (1946)
THRONE, Mildred (Mississippi Valley Historical Review) - 6 (1944, 1945)
TILESTON, Roland R. (Pomona College) - 3 (1928, 1929, n.d.)
TILLEY, Nannie M. (East Texas State Teachers College) - 3 (1946, 1950, 1956)
TIMBERLAKE, Lucie Compton (United Daughters of the Confederacy) - 2 (1933, 1934) (including 1 from Hill Turner)
TINLING, Marion (Huntington Library) - 1 (July 7, 1944)
TINSLEY, James A. (University of Houston) - 1 (June 14, 1965)
TOAL, Paul von Lilienfeld - 2 (1941)
TODD, Herbert H. (Cherokee Indian Normal School) - 9 (1934, 1936-41)
TOLSON, Hillory A. (U.S. Department of the Interior) - 1 (Jan. 8, 1938)
TOPE, R. E. (Grand Junction Public Schools) - 1 (Oct. 17, 1927)
TORCH Press, The (Edward N. Misak) - 1 (May 10, 1946)
DE LA TORRE VILLAR, Ernesto (instituto Panamericano de Geografia e His-toria) - 1 (Nov. 14, 1944)
TRAVISS, Sister Mary Peter, O.P. (Dominican College) - 1 (July 6, 1958)
TRIPPELL, Randalin (Associated Women Students of Colorado College) - 1 (May 2, 1930)
TRUETT, Randle Bond (Lincoln Institute of Kentucky) - 7 (1933, 1934, 1936, 1937)
TULLIS, Coral H. (University of Texas) - 1 (Oct. 1, 1929)
TURNER, Hill (Alumni Association of Vanderbilt University) - 1 (Nov. 16, 1936)
TURRENTINE, S. B. (Greensboro College) - 2 (1934)
UNDERWOOD, Ella Mabel - 1 (Aug. 16, 1929)
VAN HOOK, Joseph O. (Mississippi Woman's College) - 4 (1935, 1937, 1938)
VAN LEER, Blake R. (Georgia Institute of Technology) - 1 (Oct. 20, 1950)
VAN RENSSELAER, Alexander (D. Appleton-Century Company) - 2 (1936)
VAN TASSEL, David D. (The University of Texas) - 1 (Feb. 18, 1965)
VANDERBILT University Press - 1 (Apr. 3, 1942)
VAUGHAN, Elizabeth (Tulane University) - 1 (July 16, 1968)
VENABLE, Austin L. (University of Arkansas, Winthrop College) - 39 (1935, 1937-^1, 1944-46, 1948, 1949, 1952) (including 1 from Henry R. Sims)
VILES, Jonas (University of Missouri) - 2 (1936)
VOEGELI, Jacque (Tulane University) - 1 (Oct. 7, 1966)
VOLWILER, A. T. (Ohio University, Ohio War History Commission) - 11 (1938, 1939, 19H-46, 1948)
WADE, John D. (The Georgia Review) - 3 (1938, 1946)
WALKER, Curtis H. (Rice Institute, Vanderbilt University) - 39 (1923, 1923, 1926, 1929-^0, 1942, 1944-46, 1949, 1951, 1954)
WALKER, Gillian S. - 1 (July 30, 1943)
WALKER, William Edward - 1 (Dec. 24, 1947)
WALL, Bennett H. (University of Kentucky, Southern Historical Association) - 35 (1949, 1950, 1952-55, 1957-59, 1962-67) (including 1 from Clifford L. Lord and play manuscript by Gil Fite)
WALLACE, Ernest (Texas Technological College) - 2 (l943, 1967)
WALLER, Chariot (Delta Kappa Epsilon) - 1 (Apr. 14, 1951)
WALLER, G. M. (The American History Research Center) - 5 (1952-54)
WALLER, Theresa - 1 (Feb. 16, 1950)
WALLIS, C. Lamar (Rosenberg Library) - 4 (1949-50)
WALTERS, John Bennett Jr. (Emory and Henry College, Alabama College) - 29 (1936, 1944, 1946-51, 1953-56, 1962)
WALTERS, Everett (Ohio State University) - 1 (Jan. 27, 1960)
WALTHER, Daniel (Southern Junior College) - 3 (1943-46) (including 1 from W. H. Stephenson)
WARD, Judson C. Jr. (Emory University) - 1 (Dec. 22, 1949)
WARD, Paul L. (American Historical Association) - 2 (1966, 1969)
WARDELL, M. L. (University of Oklahoma) - 1 (Apr. 6, 1936)
WARDLAW, Frank H. (University of Texas Press) - 2 (1965, 1966)
WARREN, Harris G. (University of Mississippi) - 4 (l949, 1952)
WARREN, Leora R. (University of California) - 1 (Apr. 8, 1931)
WARREN, Robert Penn - 1 (Aug. 6, 1957)
WASHINGTON, Patty W. (American Historical Association) - 8 (1921, 1922, 1924, 1942, 1955) (see also: S1IAFER)
WATSON, Richard L. Jr. (Duke University, Mississippi Valley Historical Association) - 2 (1964, n.d.)
WATIS, Arthur P. (University of California, University of Pennsylvania) -3 (1910, 1918, 1930)
WEATHERFORD, J. M. (Weatherford Printing Company) - 1 (Apr. 14, 1933)
VEAVER, Blanche Henry (Clark) (Transylvania College, Vanderbilt University, National Association of Deans of Women, Georgia Teachers College, Vanderbilt-Peabody Master of Arts in Teaching) - 38 (1937, 1939-52, 1956, 1961, n.d.)
WEAVER, Herbert (Georgia Teachers College, Vanderbilt University) - 72 (1937, 1939-41, 1943-49, 1951-59, 1962, 1963, 1966, 1967, 1969) (including 1 each fromAustin Prodoehl, Guy E. Snavely, Walter B. Posey, and John Pomfret)
WEBB, Walter Prescott (University of Texas) - 23 (1929-31, 1933, 1937-39, 1941, 1949, 1951, 1953-55, 1958)
WEBER, William C. (Charles Scribner's Sons) - 1 (Oct. 24, 1944)
WEEKLEY, Glenn E. - 1 (Oct. 2, 1949)
WEEKS, Clarence N. Jr. - 2 (1954, 1959)
WEISBERGER, Bernard A. - 1 (Sept. 2, 1948)
WEISENBURGER, Francis P. (Ohio State University) - 9 (1938-41)
WELLS, Guy H. (Georgia State College for Women) - 2 (1938,;>1942>0)
WELLS, H. B. (Indiana University) - 3 (1945, 1946)
WENTWORTII, Richard L. (Louisiana State University Press) - 3 (1963)
WESLEY, Edgar B. (University of Minnesota) - 1 (May 19, 1943)
WEST, Elizabeth H. (Texas State Library) - 5 (1919, 1920, 1924)
WEST, Esther Irene (American Red Cross) - 1 (Apr. 18, 1945)
WESTERGAARD, Waldemar (Pomona College, University of California) - 3 (1924, n.d.)
WESTINGHOUSE Electric & Manufacturing Company - 3 (n.d., 1934)
WHEELER, Amie - 1 (Mar. 25, 1933)
WHEELER, Ben - 1 (July 31, 1921)
WHITAKER, Arthur P. (American Historical Association) - 1 (Jan. 4, 1946)
WHITE, Frank F. Jr. (Maryland Historical Society) - 1 (Feb. 19, 1948)
WHITE, Goodrich C. (Emory University) - 1 (Nov. 27, 1950)
WHITE, II. F. - 1 (Dec. l6, 1927)
WHITE, Robert II. (Tennessee Historical Commission, Tennessee Historical Society, Office of the State Historian) - 5 (1954, 1955, 1957, 1960)
WHITE, Weldon B. (White, Gullett, Farrell & Phillips) - 5 (1951) (including 1 each from W. F. Burton and Christopher Crittenden)
WHITEHURST, A. L. - 1 (Jan. 29, 1932)
WHITEHURST, Mrs. A. L. - 1 (Jan. 28, 1946)
WHITFIELD, Theodore M. (Western Maryland College) - 3 (1943, 1944)
WHITLEY, Sam H. (East Texas State Teachers College) - 1 (May 18, 1936)
WHITTEMORE, Robert C. (Tulane University) - 5 (1968-70)
WRITTEN, Dolphus - 1 (May 21, 1940)
WILCOX, Fannie M. (Texas State Library) - 1 (June 27, 1924)
WILEY, Bell I. (University of Mississippi, Army Ground Forces, Emory University, Louisiana State University) - 23 (1939, 1941-48, 1950)
WILEY, Evelyn (Birmingham-Southern College) - 9 (1940, 1941, 1950, 1956, 1957, 1961)
WILKERSON, M. M. (Louisiana State University Press) - 4 (1951, 1952)
WILKES, M. R. - 1 (Nov. 26, 1947)
WILLARD, Jack L. (Department of State) - 1 (Dec. 26, 1944)
WILLARD, James F. (University of Colorado, Progress of Medieval Studies) - 8 (1927-30)
WILLIAMS, Amelia (University of Texas) - 1 (Feb. 9, 1942)
WILLIAMS, Clanton W. (University of Alabama, War Department, Army Air Forces) - 9 (1936, 1938, 1939, 1941, 1942, 1944, 1946)
WILLIAMS, Frank B. Jr. ("Pappy") (East Tennessee State College) - l8 (1946, 1948-53, 1958, 1962)
WILLIAMS, Jack K. (Clemson Agricultural College) - 2 (1947)
WILLIAMS, Samuel C. (Tennessee Historical Commission; Williams, Winston & Guinn) - 23 (1941, 1942, n.d.) (including 1 each from Stanley Horn and Archibald Henderson)
WILLIAMS, T. Harry (Louisiana State University) - 26 (1943-47, 1959)
WILLIAMS, William Appleman (University of Oregon) - 1 (June 29, 1954)
WILSON, B. - 2 (1945, 1946)
WILSON, Charles R. (Colgate University) - 1 (June 14, 1945)
WILSON, Laura Mae - 1 (n.d.)
WILSON, Logan (Newcomb College) - 1 (Feb. 9, 1950)
WILSON, Osburn C. - 5 (1933-35, 1937)
WINDROW, J. E. (Peabody Demonstration School) - 1 (May l8, 1942)
WINFREY, Dorman H. (Texas State Library) - 4 (1962, 1964) (including 1 from W. Stull Holt)
WING, Herbert Jr. (Dickinson College) - 2 (1946)
WINKLER, Henry R. (The American Historical Keview) - 2 (1965)
WINSTON, A. P. (University of Texas) - 3 (1929, 1932, 1940)
WINSTON, James E. (Newcomb College) - 3 (1936)
WINTHER, Oscar O. (Indiana University) - 18 (1951, 1957-59, 1962-64)
WINTON, Dorothy (Vanderbilt University) - 1 (Apr. 12, 1939)
WIRTH, Conrad L. (U.S. Department of the Interior) - 1 (Apr. 27, 1935)
WIRTH, Fremont P. (Peabody College) - 5 (1931, 1934, n.d.) (including 1 from E. H. Stillwell)
WISH, Harvey - 3 (1943)
WITTKE, Carl (Oberlin College, Western Reserve University) - 18 (1944-46, 1951-53, 1955-57)
WOODFIN, Maude H. (University of Richmond) - 1 (Sept. 1, 1943)
WOODS, J. B. (University of Tennessee) - 1 (Oct. 27, 1953)
WOODWARD, C. Vann (Southern Historical Association) - 2 (1944, 1952)
WOODY, Robert H. (Duke University) - 17 (1936, 1937, 1942, 194-48)
WOOLPOLK, Sarah Van - 2 (1956)
WORK, Agnes (Herbert Hoover Senior High School) - 1 (Mar. 14, 1938)
WREDEN, Nicholas (E.P. Dutton & Co.) - 1 (Jan. 17, 1950)
WRIGHT, E. Baskin (University of Alabama) - 1 (Mar. 30, 1932)
WRIGHT, Louis B. (Huntington Library) - 3 (1948, 1953)
WROE, Ed. R. L., Jr. (The American National Bank) - 1 (Aug. 22, 1963)
WUEST, Lillian G. (Historical and Philosophical Society of Ohio) - 1 (Jan. 12, 1943)
WYMAN, Walter D. - 1 (Apr. 24, 1949)
YARBROUGH, W. II. (Peabody Demonstration School) - 1 (Jan. 21, 1931)
YATES, Richard E. (South Georgia College, Hendrix College) - 52 (1934-^0, 1942-46, 1949, 1957, 1958, 1966) (including 1 from Henry E. Bourne, 2 from W. T. Couch)
WENTES, Margaret B. (United Daughters of the Confederacy) - 1 (Jan. 26, 1949)
YOUNG, Donald (Social Science Research Council) - 11 (1932-34) (including 3 from Virginia Pero)
YOUNG, Harvey (Emory University) - 4 (1948, 1950, 1959)
YOUNGER, Ed (Naval War College) - 1 (Feb. 16, 1961)
YZENBAARD, John II. - 1 (Mar. l6, 1944)
ZEIGEL, Elizabeth H. (Mississippi Delta State Teachers College) - 1 (Dec. 1, 1932)
ZEPI, Erwin C. (Ohio State Archaeological and Historical Society) - 1 (Apr. 17, 1946)
ZORN, Roman J. (University of Missouri) - 1 (Jan. 20, 1951)
- BINKLEY: Incoming Correspondence — Addenda
- ABRAHAMS, Samuel, (1946); 1
- ACKEKMAN, J. D., (1930); 1
- AESCHBACHER, W. D., (1957-61, n.d.); 25
- BACARISSE, Charles and Ellie, (1963); 1
- BAILEY, J. O., (1949); 1
- BEACH, Leonard B. (Vanderbilt University), (1953); 1
- BEATSON, J. W. (National Economic League), (1929); 1
- BERGNER, Merton, (1927); 1
- BORGES, E. Gil (Pan American Union), (1925); 1; (to Erwin F. Meyer)
- BRILL, E. J., (1957); 1
- BROWN, George W. Canadian Historical Review), (1942); 1
- CLEVERDON, L. G. (Judson College), (1938); 1; (to Kenneth McDonald)
- COLE, Arthur C. (M.V.H.R.), (1935); 1
- COLE, Fred (Tulane University), (1954, 1956); 2
- COTNER, R. (University of Texas), (n.d.); 1
- COWLES, Porter (University of North Carolina Press), (1942); 1
- COX, Isaac J., (1936); (to T. R. Hay); 1
- CRITTENDEN, Christopher (North Carolina Dept. of Archives and History), (1951); 1; (to A. F. Kuhlman)
- CROWELL, J. W., (1926); 1
- CURTI, Merle (University of Wisconsin), (1945); 1
- DAVIDSON, Philip, (1948, 1951); 2
- DAVIS, Lambert (University of North Carolina Press), (1949); 1; (to G. W. Stocking)
- DAVIS, Robert E., (1964); (to W. Stull Holt); 1
- DODD, William E. (University of Chicago), (to Curtis H. Walker); 1930
- DUMOND, Dwight L. (M.V.H.A.), (1953); 2; (to C. S. Paine, M. L. Springer)
- GEER, Russel M. (Tulane University), (1955); 1
- GRIMES, Irwin L., (n.d.); 1
- HANKE, Lewis, (1941); 1; (to Prof. Nettels)
- HENDERSON, Gerald (Vanderbilt University), (1930); 1
- HESSELTINE, W. B. (University of Wisconsin), (1939); 2
- HILL, Jim Dan (Wisconsin State College), (1957); 1
- HOGAN, William R., (1954, 1956, 1957, n.d.); 8
- HORN, Stanley F. (Tennessee Historical Society), (1943); 1
- HULBERT, Archer B., (1926, n.d.); 3; (1 from Elsie Baier)
- KELLY, Alfred H. (Wayne State University), (1961); 1
- KOONTZ, Louis Knott (U.C.L.A.), (1950); 1
- KUHLMAN, A. F. (Joint University Libraries), 1; (to Earl F. Cruickshank)
- LEEBRICK, K. C., (1920); 1; (to L. L. Lewis)
- LEOPOLD, Richard W., (1963); 1; (to O. O. Winther)
- LORD, Clifford L. (State Historical Society of Wisconsin), (1952-53); 2
- LOUISIANA State University Press, (1947); 1
- LUMIANSKY, R. M. (Tulane University), (154, 1955, 1957, 1962); 7
- M.V.H.R., (1946); 1
- MARTIN, Thomas P., (1950); 2
- MAXWELL, Allen (Southwest Review), (1946); 2
- MEYER, Erwin F., (1926, 1928); 2
- MOE, Henry Allen (Guggenheim Foundation), 1
- MURPHY, Malcolm, (1926); 1
- NETTELS, Curtis P., (1942); 1
- OLSON, James C. (M.V.H.A.), (1954-56); 6
- OWSLEY, Frank L., (1933, n.d.); 2
- PAINE, Clara S. (m.v.h.a.), (1940-43, 1946, 1952, n.d.); 9
- PAINE, CUfcgfice S. (Oklahoma City Libraries), (1953, 1959); (1956, 1957); 2; peery, William (Tulane University)
- PROVINE, W. A. (Tennessee Historical Society), (1933); 1; (to F. C. Paschal)
- RAMALEY, Francis (University of Colorado), (1930); 1
- RIPPEY, J. Fred (University of Colorado), (1926); 1
- RYAN, Robert F. (Tulane University), (1970); 1
- SCHEPS, Clarence (Tulane University), (1954, 1955, 1957); 4
- SCHOLES, France, (1926); 2
- SILSBY, Robert W. (Kenmore West Senior High School), (1960); 1
- STAPLES, Dr., (1938); 1; (copy)
- STEPHENSON, W. H., (1953, n.d.); 2; (1 from Patricia Johnson)
- STOCKING, George W. (Vanderbilt University), (1953); 1
- STRAUSS, Harold (Alfred A. Knopf, Inc.), (1940); 1
- SUMMERSELL, Charles, (n.d.); 1
- TAYLOR, Garland F. (Tulane University), (1954); 2; (1 from R. E. Ellsworth)
- TODD, Herbert H. (Cherokee Indian Normal School), (1940); 1
- UNDERWOOD, Ella Mabel, (1934, 1935); 2
- UPHAW, A. H. (University of Idaho), (1921); 1
- UPTON, Lulu N., (1925); 1
- WALKER, Curtis h., (1943, 1946); 2
- WALLER, G. M. (American History Research Center), (1953); 1
- WASHINGTON, P. W. (American Historical Association), (1926); 1
- WEAVER, Herbert, (1946); 1
- WHITE, Goodrich C. (Emory University), (1948); 1
- WILEY, Bill, (1942); 1
- WILKIE, Emily D. (University of California Press), (1923, 1924); 5
- WILLIAMS, Samuel C., (1937); 1
Subject Index to Correspondence (Based on Dr. Binkley's files)
American Archivist article, 1965. See: Isabel Howell, Ken Munden.
American Association for State and Local History, 196O-1965. See William T. Alderson, Clifford L. Lord.
American Historical Association, 1956-1962. See Boyd C. Shafer.
-----. Correspondence, 1919-1950. See Howard K. Beale, J.L. Bickley, Henry E. Bourne, Elmer Ellis, Guy Stanton Ford, Ralph H. Gabriel, Lewis Hanke, Waldo G. Leland, Chester Martin, Richard L. Morton, Curtis Nettels, Dexter Perkins, Lowell Joseph Ragnatz, Conyers Read, Culver H. Smith, w.H. Stephenson, Patty W. Washington, Francis P. Weisenburger.
-----. Beveridge Fund Committee, Texas Revolutionary Correspondence, 1952-1937• See Mary Louise Almgren, J.S. Ibbotson, Bertha Joseph-son, K. D. Metcalf, Roy F. Nichols, F.S. Pease, Jr., Ulrich B. Phillips, Harriet Smither, Phelps Soule, Alexander Van Rensselaer.
-----. Harmsworth Committee, 1955- 1958. See Boyd C. Shafer, Carl Wittke.
Archives Survey correspondence, 1934-1940. See Robert Cassell, Luther H. Evans, P. M. Hamer, T. Marshall Jones, Joseph Mayer, A. R. Newsome, Frank W. Prescott.
American History Research Center, Advisory Council. See Clifford M. Lord, Forrest McDonald, George M. Waller.
Dictionary of American Biography, 1931-1941« See Ellen D. Fawcett, Dumas Malone, Harris E. Starr.
Dictionary of American History, 1938. See R. V. Coleman.
East Tennessee Historical Society, 1931-1943. See Martha L. Ellison, S. J. Folmsbee, P. M. Hamer, Jennings B. Sanders.
Fleming Lectures, 1951-1962. See Winnie Allen, A. B. Benedict, Thomas D. Clark, Robert E. Davis, Joan Doyle, Guy Stanton Ford, Marie Hammond Parker, Charles Elson Roemer, May L. Sherrard, Anne W. Smith, Charles E. Smith, Patricia Smylie, Bell I. Wiley, M. M. Wilkerson, William Appleman Williams.
Hispanic America History Review, 1923-1933. See James A. Robertson.
Journal of Southern History, 1964-1965. See Phil Detweiler.
Houston, University of, 1965-1966. See John C. Allred, Allen J. Going, John W. Meaney, Alfred R. Neumann, James A. Tinsley.
Mississippi Valley Historical Association, 1923-1944. See Ralph P. Bieber, Harold W. Bradley, Marguerite B. Haradr; George F. Howe, Clara S. Paine, Louis Pelzer, Edgar B. Wesley.
-----. Austin meeting, 1936. See Herbert E. Bolton, Arthur C. Cole, I. J. Cox, C. M. Destler, Elmer Ellis, Robert P. Felgar, Lucy Lockwood Hazard, Ernest E. Heisey, George F. Howe, Samuel A. Johnson, Bertha E. Josephson, H. C. Nixon, Clara S. Paine, Louis Pelzer, Francis B. Pinkins, Charles W. Ramsdell, Rupert N. Richardson, Siert F. Riepma, C. C. Rister, Earle D. Ross, Rebecca W. Smith, Alfred B. Thomas, M. L. Wardell, James E. Winston.
-----. Program Committee, 1937-1939. See John D, Barnhart, T. D. Clark, W. B. hesseltine, George F. Howe, V. A. Moody, J. G. Randall, C. C. Rister, J. L. Sellers, Francis P. Weisenburger.
-----. Local Arrangements, 1939. See J. L. Highsaw, Lawrence H. Levy, R. E. Logsdon.
-----. Abolition, 1938-1939. See Lewip E. Atherton, Arthur C. Cole, Bertha C. Josephson, Robert G. Lunde, Joseph C. Robert, Henry H. Simms, Francis P. Weisenberger.
-----. Mid-West Democracy, 1938-1939. See John D. Hicks, H. C. Hubbart, Jeannette P. Nichols, J. G. Randall.
-----. North-South Relations, 1938-1939. Arthur C. Cole, Avery Craven, Paul W. Gates, Herbert A. Kellar, Louis Bernard Schmidt.
-----. Spanish Interests, 1938-1939. Arthur S. Aiton, Philip C. Brooks, I. J. Cox, Charles W. Hackett, E. Wilson Lyon, Charmion Shelby, Alfred B. Thomas.
-----. Luncheon: Research Materials, 1938-1939. See: Clarence E. Carter, Charles W. Ramsdell.
-----. Great Plains, 1938-1939. See: Everett N. Dick, Louis Pelzer, C. C. Rister, Herbert S. Schell, Alfred B. Sears.
-----. Foreign Policy, 1938-1939. Seer Elmer Ellis, George F. Howe, David Thomas, A. T. Volwiler.
-----. Dinners, 1939« See: W. R. Herstein, Charles W. Ramsdell, W. H. Stevenson.
-----. Joint Session, 1938-1939. See: Gerald M. Capers, Jr., F. G. Davenport, Philip M. Hamer, Jennings B. Sanders, Mack Swearingen, Charles S. Sydnor.
-----. Humor Session, 1938-1939. See: E. Merton Coulter, A. P. Hudson, Edd Winfield Parks, William J. Peterson, John Wade.
-----. Teachers Section, 1938-1939. See: C. M. Destler, Elmer Ellis.
-----. Memphis meeting, 1939. miscellaneous. See: Theodore C. Blegen, C. M. Destler, Fletcher M. Green, B. E. Josephson, Robert P. Ludlum, William O. Lynch, Louis Pelzer, Alfred B. Sears, Richard N. Shryock, A. T. Volwiler, Francis P. Weisenberger.
-----. President, 1938-1939. See: William O. Lynch.
-----. Secretary, 1938-1938. See: Clara S. Paine.
-----. Special Committee, 1944. See: Paul M. Angle, Theodore C. Blegen, Merle Curti, E. E. Dale, Herbert A. Kellar, Harlow Lindley, William O. Lynch, Archibald MacLeish, Douglas C. McMurtrie, J. Monaghan, Stanley Pargellis, Louis Pelzer, Mildred Throne.
-----. Correspondence, 1944. See: Preston B. Albright, Matthew Page Andrews, Thomas L. Bailey, John D. Barnhart, J. Neilson Barry, Edward L. Bernays, Theodore C. Blegen, H. C. Brearley, T. D. Clark, G. N. Fuller, Colin B. Goodykoontz, J. D. Hicks, James W. Moffitt, George E. ttowry, W. S. O'Keefe, Clara S. Paine, William J. Peterson, Clayton Rand, Carl Coke Rister, Herbert S. Schell, Louis Bernard Schmidt, J. L. Sellers, Joe Patterson Smith, Mildred Throne, A. T. Volwiler, T. Harry Williams.
-----. Miscellaneous correspondence, 1944-1946. See: G. C. Barker, John D. Barnhart, Harold J. Bingham, 13. P. Brodinsky, Fred Cole, Merle Curti, E. E. Dale, Dwight L. Dumond, J. G. de Roulhac Hamilton, Robert S. Henry, A. L. Kohlmeier, William O. Lynch, Jeannette P. Nichols, Clara S. Paine, Frederic L. Paxson, Mildred W. Peker, William J. Peterson, M. M. ^uaife, Carl Coke Rister, Henrietta Thornton, H. B. Wells, Carl Wittke.
-----. Correspondence as President,-1944-1946. See: John D. Barnhart, Ray A. Billington, Theodore C. Blegen, Harold W. Bradley, T. D. Clark, Joseph E. Cross, Merle Curti, Randolph C. Downes, Luther H. Evans, Paul W. Gates, L. R. Hafen, A. L. Kohlmeier, William O. Lynch, Robert M. Magee, Jeannette P. Nichols, R. C. Overton, Clara S. Paine, Clarence S. Paine, Stuart Palmer, Louis Pelzer, M. M. Quaife, Carl Coke Rister, J. L. Sellers, Joe Patterson Smith, Mildred Throne, A.T. Volwiler, H. B. Wells, Carl Wittke.
-----. Executive Committee, 1946-1948. See: Dwight L. Agnew, O. Fritiof Ander, John D. Barnhart, Ralph P. Bieber, Theodore C. Blegen, Thomas D. Clark, Elmer Ellis, Frank Freidel, W. W. Gewehr, Colin B. Goodykoontz, Wood Gray, Fred Harvey Harrington, Herbert A. Kellar, Jean B. Kern, William O. Lynch, Clara S. Paine, Louis Pelzer, Erma Risch, Earle D. Ross, W. H. Stephenson.
-----. Correspondence, 1948-1949. See: John D. Barnhart, Kalph P. Bieber, Theodore C. Blegen, E. E. Dale, Dwight L. Dumond, Fred Harvey Harrington, Walter B. Hendrickson, Clara S. Paine, Howard H. Peckham, William J. Peterson, Carlton C. Qualley, Hubert S. Schell, J. L. Sellers.
-----. Madison meeting, 1949-1951. See: Lucille Abbott, George L. Anderson, Ralph P. Bieber, Fred Cole, Everett Dick, Dwight Dumond, Elmer Ellis, Donald B. Hoffman, Herbert A. Kellar,,George E. Mowry, Reginald C. ^cGrane, Richard C. Overton, Clara S. Paine, Clarence S. Paine, Howard H. Peckham, William J. Peterson, Carl Coke Rister, Walter D. Wyman.